Коісні Іто

Singapore

koichi.ito@u.nus.edu
 https://github.com/koito19960406 https://koichiito.com/

Research Interests

A PhD candidate at the National University of Singapore and consultant at the World Bank Group, interested in researching travel behavior, human perception, and equity with emerging spatial data sources, such as street-view imagery, and machine/deep learning techniques.

Education

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2022 - Present

PhD in Urban Analytics

Singapore

- Ongoing projects supervised by Dr. Filip Biljecki:
 - 1. EEG-based analysis of cyclists' visual perception.
 - 2. Image generation model for street view imagery.

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2019 - May 2021

Master of Urban Planning

Singapore

• 4.53/5.00 cumulative GPA (Highest Distinction)

Soka University of America

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Bachelor of Arts, Liberal Arts with Concentration in Environmental Studies

Aliso Viejo, CA

• 3.95 /4.00 cumulative GPA (summa cum laude)

Council on International Educational Exchange

• Soka University of America Merit Scholarship (US\$20,000)

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Study Abroad Program

Dakar, Senegal

Honors

Aug 2022 – Present
$\mathbf{Aug}\ 2020 - \mathbf{May}\ 2021$
May 2019
${ m Dec} 2015 - { m May} 2019$

Publications

- 9. Ito, K., et al. (2024). ZenSVI: An Open-Source Software for Integrated Acquisition, Processing and Analysis of Street View Imagery. Manuscript under review for publication in Computers, Environment and Urban Systems.
- 8. Ito, K., Bansal, P., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Examining the causal impacts of the built environment on active transportation using time-series street view imagery. Manuscript under review for publication in Transportation Research Part A: Policy and Practice.
- 7. Ito, K., Quintana, M., Han, X., Zimmermann, R., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies. International Journal of Geographical Information Science, . https://doi.org/10.1080/13658816.2024.2391969
- 6. Ito, K., Kang, Y., Zhang, Y., Zhang F., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Understanding Urban Perception with Visual Data: A Systematic Review. Cities, 152, 105169. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cities.2024.105169
- 5. Hou, Y., et al. (Ito, K.) (2024). Global Streetscapes A comprehensive dataset of millions of street-level images over 700 cities for urban science and analytics. ISPRS Journal of Photogrammetry and Remote Sensing, 215. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.isprsjprs.2024.06.023
- 4. Wang, S., et al. (Ito, K.) (2024). Mapping the landscape and roadmap of geospatial artificial intelligence (GeoAI) in quantitative human geography: An extensive systematic review. International Journal of Applied Earth Observations and Geoinformation, 128, 103734. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jag.2024.103734
- 3. Wang, Z., Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2023). Assessing the equity and evolution of urban visual perceptual quality with time series street view imagery. Cities, 145, 104704. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cities.2023.104704

- 2. Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2021). Assessing bikeability with street view imagery and computer vision. Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies, 132, 103371. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.trc.2021.103371
- 1. Biljecki, F., & **Ito**, **K.** (2021). Street view imagery in urban analytics and GIS: A review. Landscape and Urban Planning, 215, 104217. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2021.104217

Academic Services

Peer Reviews

Journal	Times Reviewed	Since
ISPRS Journal of Photogrammetry and Remote Sensing	1	2024
Scientific Data	1	2024
Philosophical Transactions A	1	2024
Urban Informatics	2	2023
International Journal of Geographical Information Science	2	2023
Landscape and Urban Planning	3	2022
Computational Urban Science	1	2023
Journal of Geographical Systems	1	2022
International Journal of Applied Earth Observation and Geoinformation	1	2022
Environment and Planning B: Urban Analytics and City Science	2	2021

Services at Organizations

• International Forum on Urbanism (IFoU): Young Ambassador

2024 – **Present**

Talks and Poster Presentations

6. "Examining the causal impacts of the built environment on cycling activities using time-series street view imagery"

Jul 2024

Chaired a session and presented at the IATBR Conference

Vienna, Austria

- 5. "Advancing urban modeling with emerging geospatial datasets and AI technologies" Feb 2024
 Gave an invited talk at the Global Space and Technology Convention 2024 Conference hosted by Singapore Land
 Authority. Singapore
- 4. "Evaluating active mobility and urban perception with visual data" Oct 2023
 Gave a guest lecture talk at a GIS course at the National University of Singapore.

 Singapore
- 3. "Sidewalk the Talk: Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies"

 Oct 2023

 Presented a poster at the Urban Solutions and Sustainability R&D Congress.

 Singapore
- 2. "Street View Imagery: Have we answered all the questions with it? What's left to do?" Sep 2023
 Chaired a session at Spatial Data Science Symposium 2023.

 Online
- 1. "Application of GIS in research and international institution."

 Presented my research at Soka University of America, Advanced GIS Course.

 Online

Work Experience

The World Bank Group — Poverty and Equity Global Practice

Apr 2021 - Present

Consultant

Remote

- Developed and maintained interactive data dashboards using Shiny and Golem frameworks to facilitate spatial data visualization and analysis.
- Implemented spatial lag models in R to analyze factors correlated with poverty and stunting.
- Led the collection, cleaning, and mapping of various spatial data sets to predict poverty rates in developing countries with XGBoost in Python.
- Conducted a capacity-building program for Tanzania's National Bureau of Statistics, imparting skills and knowledge on spatial analysis using R.

Johnson Controls

Nov 2020 - May 2021

 $Data\ Analytics\ Intern$

Singapore

• Constructed a data pipeline of PM2.5 data, weather data, and traffic data in Singapore on Azure Synapse for a real-time Power BI dashboard.

• Built a time-series model to predict PM 2.5 levels anywhere in Singapore with Python.

The World Bank Group — Tokyo Development Learning Center

Urban Development Research Intern

Apr 2020 – Jan 2021

• Compiled comprehensive data set of over 4,000 Tokyo-based startups' information, such as addresses, investors, and

- accelerators, using Python.
- Visualized financial performance of light rail transport system in Toyama prefecture between 2002 and 2019.

ENDA LEAD Afrique Francophone

Research Intern

Dakar, Senegal

Remote

• Authored a report on accessibility to potable water in 500 villages in the Saint-Louis region in Senegal.

Teaching Experience

CDE2212 AI for Design

Aug 2024 - Dec 2024

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

 Assisted in a comprehensive course on AI applications in design (generative models), providing in-person and online support during weekly lectures and tutorials, conducting lab sessions, and grading.

DEP5111 Planning Technologies

Jan 2024 - May 2024

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

 Assisted Master of Urban Planning students in mastering R Data Science through hands-on coding support, troubleshooting, and grading, enhancing their data analysis and visualization skills.

AR5805 Advanced Architecture Studio

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

 Assisted the lead professor with logistical and administrative tasks, including the preparation of course documents and aiding in the smooth operation of lectures.

Supervising

• Shu Wang: Master of Applied GIS, the National University of Singapore

Apr 2024 - Jul 2024

• Heyang Hua: Master of Urban Planning, the National University of Singapore

Jan 2024 - May 2024

• Zeyu Wang: Master of Urban Planning, the National University of Singapore

Aug 2022 - May 2023

Technical Skills

Languages: Japanese (native), English (fluent), French (limited working proficiency)

Computer Skills: Python, R, SQL, Spark, ArcGIS, QGIS, Google Earth Engine, Azure, AWS, Power BI

References

· Filip Biljecki Presidential Young (Assistant) Professor College of Design and Engineering, The National University of Singapore

• Prateek Bansal Presidential Young (Assistant) Professor College of Design and Engineering, The National University of Singapore

· Zhang Ye Associate Professor School of Architecture, Tsinghua University

• Takaaki Masaki Senior Economist The World Bank, Poverty & Equity Global Practice